Thanks for your interest in this course.
I'm MK and I have been working in software industry for the past 15 years.
I'm a great fan of Android and AOSP project.
Over the years, Android has captured mobile phones, tablets, TV, web devices, auto, motive
and many other embedded devices.
It's running in 2.5 billion active.
Two devices, even though Android has been in the market S for such a long time, it's
still pretty hard to find structured courses or online resources for AOSP development.
That's the reason we thought of making this course.
This course is specially designed for developers of any level who wants to learn about,
developing Android OS, focusing more on mobile development.
This course is also helpful for Android application developers.
You can be a better programmer when you know more about the Android OS internals.
We have tried to make this course as compact as possible so that you can learn something
new, each minute of the tutorials.
On a very high level, the course is structured as follows.
The course starts with a basics of AOSP development, like architecture, environment setup
and ends with advanced topics like solinox, system services, SDK addons and so on.
Kindly have a look at the latest course curriculum under the course content.
The course is perfect for those new to AOSP world or who wants to learn more about different
aspects of AOSP development.
At the end of the course, you should gain enough knowledge to create your own Android version.
Please feel free to ask me questions if you need any support while taking the course.
Thank you and all the very best.